integrysgroup.com 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy (Integrys Energy Group)

[Home Page](http://www.integrysgroup.com/default.aspx)  > Privacy Policy  >

## Integrys Energy Group, Inc. (Integrys)  
Website Privacy Policy

_(Revised May 30, 2012)_

Integrys Energy Group (also referred to as "we" or "us") is concerned about preventing unauthorized disclosure of customer information. We understand the importance you place on the privacy and security of information that personally identifies you or your account information. We refer to this information as "personal information." We want you to know what personal information we collect and how we use it. We have therefore adopted the following Privacy Policy to explain our commitment to your privacy. If you have any questions about our policy after reading it, please [contact us](https://accel.integrysgroup.com/secure/ssl/contact.aspx "Contact Us").

By using the website, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. Please check this policy frequently, as we may amend it from time to time to reflect changes in our services and our policies relating to customer information. Amendments will become effective at the time they are posted on our website. We will not provide notice of changes in this Privacy Policy.

  * Personal Information
  * Visitor Information
  * Our Use of Your IP Address
  * Our Use of Cookies
  * Links to Other Sites

### Personal Information

You may be asked to submit personal information such as your name, address, phone number and email address. We will protect all information that you provide us on the website, as set forth below:

  1. The personal information you provide us not only enables you to access various services offered on the website, but also enables us to provide you with better service. We may use this information to contact you to respond to an inquiry that you send to TEG. If you choose to communicate with TEG by email, then email from TEG to you will be considered to be sent with your consent and will be accessible to anyone who has access to your email.
  2. In order to provide you with services offered on the website, or to complete transactions or requests initiated by you on the website, we may transfer you to a website operated by third parties that help us provide services to you. In such cases, we will have agreements with those parties under which they will agree to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and to use it only for the purpose of helping us serve you. We only transfer or share information to those who have a privacy policy at least as stringent or substantially similar to TEG.
  3. Other than as set forth herein, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your written consent (which consent may be obtained electronically, such as by email), unless we reasonably believe that the disclosure is essential to the conduct of TEG's business, including but not limited to where such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with the law, legal process or our regulators, (b) collect unpaid bills, (c) enable TEG's employees or consultants to provide service to you and to otherwise perform their duties, (d) comply with interchange functions, (e) obtain and provide credit reporting information, or (f) resolve customer disputes or inquiries. We do not provide your personal information to third parties for the purpose of telemarketing, email or direct-mail solicitation.
  4. You should protect the confidentiality of your username and password. You are responsible for all activity on the website accessed by your username and password. Access by TEG's employees or consultants to any personal information you provide is limited to only that necessary to provide the business service offered and to otherwise allow such employees or consultants to perform their duties.

Back to Top

### Visitor Information

We do collect information about the website use, such as the number of visitors to the website and the number of users that click on certain links or services. For some applications, we link usage information with the particular customer visiting the website. We use industry standard software to create summary statistics of the usage data we collect, which may then be used to highlight what our visitors find interesting, to improve our website design specifications, to identify system performance issues, and for other internal purposes.

Back to Top

### Our Use of Your IP Address

An Internet Protocol ("IP") address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer every time that you browse the Internet. When you visit the website, our servers log your current IP address. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website. Data gathered from logging your IP address is not tied to your personal information and is not used to identify you.

Back to Top

### Our Use of Cookies

Cookies are small text files placed on your computer's hard drive by Web page servers. When you visit the website, our server may create "session" cookies, making it more convenient for you to use our site by verifying when you travel from page to page that you have signed up with our online services.

The website may use cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches.

TEG and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with TEG more convenient and personal.

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

In some of our email messages, we use a "click-through URL" linked to content on the TEG website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

Back to Top

## Links to Other Sites

While browsing the website, you may encounter hypertext links to other websites operated by third parties. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, log your IP address, and otherwise collect data or solicit personal information.

**We do not control and are not responsible for what third parties do in connection with their websites, or how they handle your personal information. Please exercise caution and consult the privacy policies posted on such websites for further information.**

If you have any questions about this policy, please [contact us](https://accel.integrysgroup.com/secure/ssl/contact.aspx "Contact Us").

Back to Top
